Guide to the Frick Fine Arts Library Artist Files, 1892-1990 FFAL.002
ULS Frick Fine Arts Library
- Multiple Artist Files, I.; 259 folders
  - Das-Dau (File-cabinet 3, Drawer 2, Folder 59)
    Includes reproductions of Daumier paintings: "Le Haleur" and "Le Fardeau" sold at Hotel Drouot, Paris, May 28, 1910; provenance and exhibition information for "Les Amateurs D'Estampes," "La Parade des Saltimbanques," and "La Ronde" through 1928.
    Da Silva, Alfredo; Dasburg, Andrew, 1887-1979; Dater, Judy; Dauchot, Gabriel, 1926-; Daugherty, James, 1889-1974; Daumier, Honoré, 1808-1879
  - Dav-Daz (File-cabinet 3, Drawer 2, Folder 60)
    Davey, Randall, 1887-1964; Davids, Dorothy Lauer; Davidson, Jo, 1883-1952; Davie, Alan, 1920-2014; Davies, Arthur B. (Arthur Bowen), 1862-1928; Davies, Jordan; Davis, April; Davis, Brad, 1942-; Davis, Gene; Davis, Gladys Rockmore; Davis, Jack; Davis, Robert T.; Davis, Ronald, 1937-; Davis, Stuart, 1892-1964; Davison, Nancy R.; Daws, Lawrence, 1927-; Day, Larry
  - Db-Deh (File-cabinet 3, Drawer 2, Folder 61)
    Includes reproductions of two paintings by Edgar Degas: "Au Champ de Courses" and Le Foyer de la Danse a l'opera" along with provenance and exhibition information through 1928.
    De Andrea, John, 1941-; De Coux, Janet, 1904-1999; De Creeft, José, 1884-1982; De Diego, Julio, 1900-1979; De Fazio, Raymond; Deaton, Herman; Deaton, Neal; Debras, Louis; Decker, Barbara; DeCock-Morgan, Liliane; Deem, George, 1932-2008; DeForest, Roy, 1930-2007; Degas, Edgar, 1834-1917; Degrand, Joel; Dehn, Adolf, 1895-1968
  - Dei-Del (File-cabinet 3, Drawer 2, Folder 62)
    De Kooning, Willem, 1904-1997; De Lamonica, Roberto; de Leon, Amanda; De Lucca, Yargo, 1925-; Deitch, Sande; Delacroix, Eugène, 1798-1863; Delafield, David; DeLaunay, Sonia; Delfin, Victor; Delhez, Victor, 1902-; Dell, Betty Lou; Della Torre, Enrico, 1931-; Della, Ben; Deloache, James; Delobbe, François-Alfred; DeLonga, Leonard, 1925-
  - Dem-Dez (File-cabinet 3, Drawer 2, Folder 63)
    Includes 1976 catalog of art for sale by William Wallace Denslow, illustrator of the first editions of the "Wizard of Oz."
    De Niro, Robert, Sr., 1922-1993; de Vera, Virginia; Demmler, Fred; Demonchy, André; Demuth, Charles, 1883-1935; Denney, Jim, 1953-; Dennison, Dorothy; Denny, Robyn, 1930-2014; Denslow, W. W. (William Wallace), 1856-1915; DePasse, Kathi; Derain, André, 1880-1954; DeRome, Albert Thomas, 1885-1959; DeRose, Susan; Desmett, Ron, 1948-; Detaille, Edouard, 1848-1912; Detwiller, Frederick Knecht; Devlin, Lucinda; Devlin, Richard; Dewasne, Jean
  - Df-Dit (File-cabinet 3, Drawer 2, Folder 64)
    Diao, David, 1943-; Diaz Cortés, Antonio; Diaz de la Peña, Narcisse Virgile, 1807-1876; Diaz, Julia; Dibbetts, Jan; Dickerman, Seth; Dickinson, Edwin Walter, 1891-1978; Dickinson, Preston, 1889-1930; Dickstein, Alvin; Diebenkorn, Richard, 1922-1993; Diefenbacher, Ron; Dieffenbach, Anton Heinrich; Diehl, Hans-Jürgen, 1940-; Dieterle, Marie; Dilsizian, Ggarbiss; Dine, Jim, 1935-; Dininno, Frank; Dinneen, Alice; Dinsmore, Grant; Diomede, Miguel, 1902-1974; Ditillo, Poki; Dittberner, Martin, 1912; Dittrich, Simon, 1940-
  - Diu-Dol (File-cabinet 3, Drawer 2, Folder 65)
    Dix, Harry; Dixon, Maynard, 1875-1946; Dmitrienko, Pierre, 1925-1974; Doan, William Sayles; Dobashi, Jun; Dodd, Lamar; Dodd, Lois, 1927-; Doesburg, Theo van, 1883-1931; Dogançay, Burhan, 1929-2013; Dole, William, 1917-1983; Dolphin, Frank
  - Dom-Doz (File-cabinet 3, Drawer 2, Folder 66)
    Dombrowski, Ernst von, 1896-1985; Domela, 1900-1992; Dominat, Paul; Domjan, Joseph, 1907-1992; Dōmoto, Hisao, 1928-2013; Donahue, Vic; Donaldson, Jeff, 1932-2004; Donneson, Seena; Dorazio, Piero, 1927-2005; Dorfman, Bruce, 1936-; Dotremont, Christian, 1922-1979; Douglas, Elizabeth Asche; Doutreleau, Pierre, 1938-; Dove, Arthur Garfield, 1880-1946; Dowell, John; Dowell, John, 1941-; Downing, Joe, 1925-2007; Doyle, Tom; Dozier, Otis, 1904-1987
  - Dp-Dud (File-cabinet 3, Drawer 2, Folder 67)
    Dramard, Georges de; Draper, William F., 1912-2003; Drescher, Ruth; Drewes, Werner, 1899-1985; Drexel, (Hans) Christof, 1886-1979; Drexler, Sherman; Drisch, Russell; Driskell, David, 1963-; Drudis, Jose; Drum, Sydney; Dubin, Ralph; DuBois, Guy Pene; Dubuffe, Guillame; Duca, Alfred M.; Dudchenko, Boris; Dudchenko, Nancy
  - Due-Dup (File-cabinet 3, Drawer 2, Folder 68)
    Dufresne, Charles, 1876-1938; Dufy, Jean, 1888-1964; Dufy, Raoul, 1877-1953; Dugan, George; Dujardin-Beaumetz, Etienne; Dunkle, Alvin; Dunlevy, Ray; Dunoyer de Segonzac, André, 1884-1974; Dupré, Jules, 1811-1889; Dupre, Victor
  - Duq-Dz (File-cabinet 3, Drawer 2, Folder 69)
    Includes 1929 exhibition catalog: "Engravings and Etchings by Albrecht Durer," M. Knoedler & Co., Inc., New York.
    Durchanek, Ludvik; Dürer, Albrecht, 1471-1528; Dutary, Alberto; Dworkowitz, Alan; Dwyer, James; Dzierzynski, André, 1936-; Dzigurski, Alexander, 1911-; Dzubas, Friedel, 1915-1994
  - Ea-Eb (File-cabinet 3, Drawer 2, Folder 70)
    Includes 1945 exhibition catalog: "Thomas Eakins Centennial Exhibition 1844-1944," Carnegie Institute.
    Eades, Luis; Eagerton, Robert; Eakin, Alice; Eakins, Thomas, 1844-1916; Earl, Jack, 1934-; Eaton, Myrwyn; Eberle, Abastenia St. Leger 1878-; Eberle, Edward
  - Ec-Ei (File-cabinet 3, Drawer 2, Folder 71)
    Echeverri, Beatriz; Echeverría, Enrique, 1923-1972; Economos, Gérard; Edelson, Mary Beth; Edlich, Stephen; Edmondson, William; Edson, Gary; Edwards, Herb, 1894-; Efrat, Benni, 1936-; Egar, Efrain Garcia Abadia; Egells, Paul; Egenau, Juan, 1927-1987; Eggenhofer, Nicholas, 1897-1985; Eggers, W. P. Eberhard (Wilhelm Paul Eberhard), 1939-; Eichelbaum, Edward W.; Eichenberg, Fritz, 1901-1990; Eilshemius, Louis M. (Louis Michel), 1864-1941
  - Ej-Eq (File-cabinet 3, Drawer 2, Folder 72)
    Includes 1931 El Greco exhibition catalog: "Catalog of a Group of Paintings by the Master of the Sixteenth Century Dominico Theotocopuli (El Greco)," The Buffalo Fine Arts Academy.
    Eishirō, Abe, 1902-1984; El Greco, 1541?-1614; Elias, Harold J.; Elk, Ger van, 1941-; Elliot, Ronnie; Elliott, Anne, 1764-1825; Ellis, Andra; Ellis, Dean, 1920-2009; Ellis, Robert M.; Ellwood, Evelyn; Elmer, Edwin Romanzo, 1850-1923; Emergy, Jeanne E.; Emerson, Edith, 1888-1965; Emery, Priscilla; Emett, Rowland, 1906-; Enault, Alix Louise; Endacott, Pamela; Ender, Thomas, 1793-1875; Engel, Jules, 1909-2003; Enneking, John J., 1841-1916; Ensor, James, 1860-1949; Enters, Angna, 1897-1989
  - Er-Ez (File-cabinet 3, Drawer 2, Folder 73)
    Includes 1974 press releases from the National Gallery of Art regarding new M. C. Escher acquisitions.
    Erdle, Rob; Erenberg, Samuel; Erla, Karen, 1942-; Erni, Hans, 1909-2015; Ernst, Jimmy, 1920-1984; Escalier, Nicolas Felix; Escher, Fred; Escher, M. C. (Maurits Cornelis), 1898-1972; Etnier, Stephen, 1903-1984; Etrog, Sorel, 1933-; Etting, Emlen, 1905-1993; Evans, Donald, 1940-; Evans, Frederick H.; Evans, Garth, 1934-; Evans, Merlyn, 1910-1973; Eve, Jean, 1900-1968; Evergood, Philip, 1901-1973; Evett, Kenneth, 1913-2005; Ewing, Buck; Ewing, C. Kermit
  - Fa (File-cabinet 3, Drawer 2, Folder 74)
    Fabergé, Peter Carl, 1846-1920; Fabien, Louis, 1952-; Fabrès, Oscar, 1894-1960; Fabri, Ralph, 1894-; Fairbanks, Avard T. (Avard Tennyson), 1897-1987; Falkenstein, Claire, 1908-1997; Fanning, Ralph, 1889-1971; Fantin-Latour, Henri; Faragó, Miklós; Farbstein, Sheri; Farley, Ken; Farley, Rachel; Farmer, Bart; Farny, Henry F.; Faulkner, Barry, 1881-1966; Fax, Eleanor; Fay, Ming, 1943-; Faz, Carlos, 1931-1953
  - Fb-Fer (File-cabinet 3, Drawer 2, Folder 75)
    Fearing, Kelly; Febo, Nicola; Feshin, Nikolaĭ Ivanovich, 1881-1955; Fedier, Franz, 1922-; Fein, H. O. (H. Otto); Fein, Sylvia; Feinberg, Ellen; Feitelson, Lorser, 1898-1978; Feldman, Eugene, 1921-1975; Fell, Sheila, 1931-1979; Fennell, Michelle Talibah; Fenton, Beatrice, 1887-1983; Fenton, John Nathaniel, 1912-1977; Ferber, Herbert, 1906-1991; Fernandez, Augustin; Ferren, John, 1905-1970; Ferrer, Rafael; Ferretti, Giovanni Domenico, 1692-1768; Ferris, Hugh; Ferris, Warren; Ferstman, Gerald
  - Fes-Fio (File-cabinet 3, Drawer 2, Folder 76)
    Field, Frances; Fiene, Ernest, 1894-1966; Fieschi, Giannetto, 1921-; Filcer, Luis, 1927-; Filkosky, Josefa; Finch, Dennis; Finch, Keith, 1966-; Fine, Jamie; Fineberg, Judi; Fink, Larry; Fink, Sam; Fiore, Joseph, 1925-2008; Fiorello, Sabato
  - Fip-Fon (File-cabinet 3, Drawer 2, Folder 77)
    Finch, Thomas Martin; Fischer, Anton Otto, 1882-1962; Fischer, Hans, 1909-1958; Fischer, R. M., 1947-; Fish, Janet, 1938-; Fisher, Alvin; Fisher, Thomas; Fishman, Richard, 1941-; Fitzgerald, James; Fitzpatrick, Joseph; Flack, Audrey; Flanigan, James; Flavin, Dan, 1933-1996; Fleischner, Richard, 1944; Flers, Camille; Flint, William Russell,, 1880-1969; Floch, Joseph, 1895-1977; Florsheim, Richard; Floyd, Tina; Fogel, Seymour, 1911-1984; Folkman, David; Fonssagrives-Penn, Lisa; Fontana, Lucio, 1899-1968
  - Foo-For (File-cabinet 3, Drawer 2, Folder 78)
    Forain, Jean Louis, 1852-1931; Forbát, Alfréd, 1897-1972; Ford, Barbara J.; Ford, Lauren, 1891-; Forner, Raquel, 1902-1988; Forrestall, Tom, 1936-; Forsman, Chuck; Forte, Vicente; Fortess, Karl E. (Karl Eugene), 1907-; Fortuna, Delores
  - Fos-Fran (File-cabinet 3, Drawer 2, Folder 79)
    Foster, Tony, 1946-; Fox, Susan, 1956-; Fragonard, Honoré, 1732-1806; Frailong, Pierre; Franceschini, Aldo (Maria); Francis, Sam; Francis, Sherron; Franck, Frederick, 1909-2006; Franco, Huguette; Frank, John L.; Frank, Mary, 1919-; Frank, Robert; Frankfurter, Jack, 1929-; Frantz, Alison
  - Frao-Fre (File-cabinet 3, Drawer 2, Folder 80)
    Frary, Michael, 1918-; Frasconi, Antonio; Fraser, James Earl; Frazao, Armando; Frazier, Kenneth, 1867-1949; Freborg, Stan; Freed, David, 1936-; Freedman, Maurice, 1904-1985; Freid, Hilda; Freid, Sam; Freiman, Lillian; Freire, Maria; French, Clark J.; French, Daniel Chester, 1850-1931; French, Elaine; Freund, Jane; Freund, Tibor; Frey, Viola, 1933-2004
  - Fri-Fz (File-cabinet 3, Drawer 2, Folder 81)
    Fricano, Tom; Friedeberg, Pedro, 1937-; Friedlander, Lee; Friedman, James, 1958-; Friedman, Martin, 1937-; Friedrich, Caspar David, 1774-1840; Friesz, Achille-Emile-Othon, 1879-1949; Frigerio, Ismael, 1955-; Frishmuth, Harriet Whitney, 1880-1980; Frith, Bedford; Frost, J.O.J. (John Orne Johnson) 1852-1928.; Frost, Stuart H.; Froysaa, Knut; Fruchter, Louis; Fuchs, Emil, 1866-1929; Fuente, Manuel de la; Fuertes, Louis Agassiz, 1874-1927; Fugate-Wilcox, Terry; Fugikawa, Gyo; Fuller, Buckminster, 1895-1983; Fussiner, Howard; Fussmany, Klaus
  - Gaa-Gan (File-cabinet 3, Drawer 2, Folder 82)
    Gabo, Naum, 1890-1977; Gaede, Marc; Gaertner, Carl, 1898-1952; Gaffney, Jim; Gailliot, Mary Anne; Gaitis, Conosco Yannis; Galantiere, Nancy; Galicia, Jose Luis; Gallagher, Michael, 1941-; Gallas, Ron; Gallatin, Albert Eugene, 1881-1952; Gallatin, Gaile; Gallick, Terry; Gallo, Frank, 1933-; Galloway, John C.; Gammeter, Elmer; Gandy; Ganso, Emil, 1895-1941; Gantner, Bernard, 1928
  - Gao-Gar (File-cabinet 3, Drawer 2, Folder 83)
    Gaputye, Elena; Garabedian, Charles; Garavaglia, Florenco; Garbell, Alexandre, 1903-1970; Garber, Daniel, 1880-1958; Garcia, Torres; Garcia-Llort, Jose; Gardette, Louis; Gardner, Clark; Gardner, Elizabeth Jane, 1837-1922; Gardner, Mark; Garnett, Porter,1871-1951; Garsoian, Inna, 1896-1984
  - Gas-Gel (File-cabinet 3, Drawer 2, Folder 84)
    Includes reproductions of two paintings by Paul Gauguin: "La Orana Maria" and "Pasyage Exotique" along with provenance and exhibition information through 1928.
    Gash, Gail; Gaskins, John; Gaspard, Leon; Gasser, Henry M., 1909-1981; Gates, Jack, 1955-; Gatto, Domingo; Gauguin, Paul, 1848-1903; Gault, Martha; Gaveau, Claude, 1940-; Gechtoff, Sonia, 1926-; Geddes, Norman Bel, 1893-1958; Gego; Gehr, Mary; Gelb, Jan, 1906-1978; Gelder, Aert de, 1645-1727; Gelpi, Rene
  - Gem-Geo (File-cabinet 3, Drawer 2, Folder 85)
    Genis, René; Gennadiev; Genovés, Juan, 1930-; Gent, Cock van; Gentilz, Theodore, 1906-; Geoffroy, Jean; George, Diane W.; George, Herbert; Georges, Claude, 1929-1988
  - Gep-Gik (File-cabinet 3, Drawer 2, Folder 86)
    Gérôme, Jean Léon, 1824-1904; Gerstein, Noemi; Gervex, Henri, 1852-1929; Geyra, Don; Ghirlandajo, Ridolfo; Giacometti, Alberto, 1901-1966; Giacometti, Bruno,1907-2012; Giacometti, Diego; Gialamas, Frances; Gibbons, Bud; Gibran, Kahlil, 1883-1931; Gikow, Ruth, 1915-1982
  - Gil-Gla (File-cabinet 3, Drawer 2, Folder 87)
    Includes 1966-1967 William Glackens traveling exhibition catalog: "William Glackens in Retrospect."
    Gilhooly, David; Gill, John Patrick; Gillespie, Dorothy, 1920-; Gillespie, Gregory; Gilmour, Lloyd S.; Gilot, Françoise, 1921-; Gironella, Albert; Glackens, William, 1870-1938; Glabicki, Paul; Glarner, Fritz, 1899-1972; Glasco, Joseph, 1925-1996; Glasgow, Robert; Gindele, Terry; Glabicki, Paul; Glazunov, Ilia
  - Gle-Gog (File-cabinet 3, Drawer 2, Folder 88)
    Includes reproductions of three paintings by Vincent van Gogh: "Le Facteur Roulin," "Arles: le Pont de Trinquetaille," and "Les Lauriers Roses" along with provenance and exhibition information through 1928.
    Glicenstein, Enrico,1870-1942; Glickman, Maurice; Glück, Heidi; Gluckmann, Grigory, 1898-1973; Godard, Gabriel, 1933-; Godfrey, Diana; Godwin, Judith; Goedike, Shirl; Goeldi, Oswaldo, 1895-1961; Goff, Bruce, 1904-1982; Gogh, Vincent van, 1820-1888
  - Goh-Gom (File-cabinet 3, Drawer 2, Folder 89)
    Gold, Rae; Goldberg, Lenore; Goldberg, Michael, 1950-; Goldberg, Paul; Goldin, Leon, 1923-; Goldman, Bunny; Goldring, Milton; Goldstein, Daniel Joshua, 1950-; Golinkin, Jo; Golub, Leon, 1922-2004; Gomez-Molina, Lilian
  - Gon-Gor (File-cabinet 3, Drawer 2, Folder 90)
    Góngora, Leonel; González Goyri, Roberto;González, Julio; Gonzalez, Ronald, 1952-; Gonzalez, Xavier, 1898-1993; Good, Dalton; Goode, Dale Anthony; Goodlow, Joan; Goodman, Eileen; Goodman, Sidney; Goodnough, Robert, 1917-2010; Gordin, Sidney; Gordon, Carol Schwab; Gordon, Harvey, 1941-; Gordy, Robert, 1933-1986; Gorgzyca, Robert; Gorin, Jean, 1899-1981; Gorky, Arshile, 1904-1948; Gorson, Aaron Harry, 1872-1933
  - Gos-Goz (File-cabinet 3, Drawer 2, Folder 91)
    Includes 1955 Francisco Goya traveling exhibition catalog: "Goya Drawings and Prints."
    Gos, Albert, 1852-1942; Goto Matabee; Goto, Joseph, 1920-; Gottlieb, Adolph, 1903-1974; Goulet, Lorrie, 1925-; Gourevitch, Jacqueline; Gourfain, Peter; Goya, Francisco, 1746-1828
  - Gp-Grat (File-cabinet 3, Drawer 2, Folder 92)
    Grabhorn, Edwin; Grabhorn, Robert; Grabowski, Jerry; Grachis, Dimitri; Graham, John, 1940-; Gramatté, Walter, 1897-1929; Gramcko, Elsa, 1925-1994; Granado, Carlos; Granlund, Paul; Grant, James; Grant, Susan Kae; Grassman, Marcelo
  - Grau-Graz (File-cabinet 3, Drawer 2, Folder 93)
    Grau, Enrique, 1920-2004; Grau-Garriga, Josef; Graupe-Pillard, Grace; Graves, Abbott; Graves, Nancy, 1940-1995; Gray, Cleve, 1918-2004; Gray, Don, 1926-; Graybrook, Michael
  - Gre-Gris (File-cabinet 3, Drawer 2, Folder 94)
    Green, Denise Suska; Green, G. D. (George Dennis), 1928-; Green, Rita Martin; Greenbaum, Marty; Greene, Gertrude, 1904-1956; Greene, Glenn; Greeves, Richard V.; Grey, Alex,; Grieshaber, Hap, 1909-1981; Griffin, Tony, 1954-; Griffith, Marie; Grillo, John, 1917-2014; Grilo, Sarah; Grippe, Peter, 1912-; Gris, Juan, 1887-1927; Grison, Adolphe
  - Grit-Grop (File-cabinet 3, Drawer 2, Folder 95)
    Groer, Dona; Groer, Walter; Grolleron, Paul; Grooms, Red; Grooms, Reginald L. (Reginald Leslie), 1900-1989; Gropius, Walter, 1883-1969; Gropper, William, 1897-1977
  - Groq-Groz (File-cabinet 3, Drawer 2, Folder 96)
    Grosperrin, Claude; Gross, Anthony, 1905-1984; Gross, Earl; Gross, Hermann, 1903-2002; Grosser, Maurice, 1903-1986; Grossi, Emilio; Grossman, Morton; Grosz, George, 1893-1959; Groth, Jan, 1938-
  - Gru-Gua (File-cabinet 3, Drawer 2, Folder 97)
    Gruber, Aaron DeRoy; Grünewald, Matthias; Guacci, Italo; Guayasamín, Oswaldo
  - Gub-Gz (File-cabinet 3, Drawer 2, Folder 98)
    Gubler, Max, 1898-1973; Sigurður Guðmundsson, 1942-; Guerrini, Lorenzo, 1914-2002; Guevara-Moreno, Luis; Guglielmi, Louis; Guignard, Alberto da Veiga, 1896-1962; Guillen, Asilia; Gummelt, Sam; Gunner, Jean; Gunthart, Lotte, 1914-; Guston, Philip, 1913-1980; Gutmann, Willi, 1927-; Gutowski, John W.; Guttuso, Renato, 1911-1987; Guy, Betty; Guy, James; Guyer, Henry; Guzman-Reyes, Luis; Gwathmey, Robert, 1903-1988; Servulo, Gutierrez
  - Haa-Hal (File-cabinet 3, Drawer 2, Folder 99)
    Haacke, Hans, 1936-; Haas, Michel, 1934-; Haber, Sandra; Haberle, John, 1856-1933; Haden, Sir Francis Seymour; Hadzi, Dimitri, 1921-2006; Hagin, Nancy, 1940-; Hain, Claude;Holbrook, Hollis, 1909-1984; Holgate, Jeanne; Holland, Harry, 1911-1996; Hollander, Irwin; Hollar, Wenceslaus,1607-1677; Hollen-Bolmgren, Donna; Holley, Douglas; Hollon, Belle; Holt, Martha A.; Hölzel, Adolf, 1853-1934; Honegger, Gottfried, 1917-; Hood, Dorothy, 1918-2000; Hoog, Bernard de; Hook, Dorothy Haines, Richard, 1906-1984; Halahmy, Oded, 1938-; Hall, Christopher, 1930-; Hall, Douglas Kent, 1952-; Hallam, Beverly, 1923-; Hallman, H. Theodore Jr.; Halsey, William, 1915-1999
  - Ham-Harm (File-cabinet 3, Drawer 2, Folder 100)
    Hambourg, André, 1909-1999; Hamilton, Helen; Hammer, Victor, 1882-1967; Hamwi, Richard; Haney, William; Hanna, David, 1967-; Hansen, Job, 1899-1960; Hansen, Robert, 1945-; Hanson, Bill; Hanson, Duane; Hanson, J. M. (Joseph Miles), 1868-1921; Harbeson, Georgiana Brown, 1894-1980; Hardy, Tom; Hare, Channing; Hare, Clyde; Hare, David, 1917-1992; Harms, Elizabeth
  - Harn-Harz (File-cabinet 3, Drawer 3, Folder 101)
    Includes two William M. Harnett exhibition catalogs: "Nature-Vivre" 1939, The Downtown Gallery, NY, and "Harnett Centennial Exhibition" 1948, The Downtown Gallery.
    Harnett, William M.; Harpignies, Henri Joseph; Harris, Michael, 1933-1994; Harris, Paul, 1925-; Harris, Phil, 1939-; Harris, Teenie, 1908-1998; Harrison, Newton, 1932-; Harshe, Robert B., 1879-1938; Hart, Agnes; Hart, James; Hart, William; Hartell, John Anthony, 1902-1995; Hartl, Léon, 1889-; Hartley, Marsden, 1877-1943; Hartung, Hans, 1904-1989; Harvan, George, 1921-; Harvey, Donald E.; Harvey, Eli, 1860-1957; Harvey, James, 1929-
  - Has-Hav (File-cabinet 3, Drawer 3, Folder 102)
    Haskell, Jane; Hassall, John, 1868-1948; Hassam, Childe, 1859-1935; Hatcher, Brower, 1942-; Haucke, Frederick; Hausman, Fred, 1921-; Havard, James, 1937-
  - Haw-Hei (File-cabinet 3, Drawer 3, Folder 103)
    Hawthorne, Charles W. (Charles Webster), 1872-1930; Hayden, Palmer C., 1890-1973; Hayden, Sophia, 1868-1953; Hayes, David V.; Hayes, Marvin,1926-1995; Hayman, Patrick, 1915-1988; Hayter, Stanley William, 1901-1988; Hayward, Colleen; Heade, Martin J.; Healy, Anne; Hecht, Zoltan; Heckel, Erich. 1883-1970; Hedman, Donn; Heideman, Susan; Heikka, Earle E.; Heindorff, Michael, 1949-; Heinecken, Robert F.; Heinsius, Johann Ernst, 1740-1812; Heintzelman, Arthur W. (Arthur William), 1891-1965; Heiss, Alanna; Heizer, Michael, 1944-
  - Hej-Hem (File-cabinet 3, Drawer 3, Folder 104)
    Hekking, William M.; Held, Al, 1928-2008; Held, Lloyd Cansino; Heliker, John, 1909-2000; Helleu, Paul-Cesar; Hellman, Edith, 1873-; Helm, Alison; Helmūts, Inārs, 1934-; Hendricks, James, 1938-
  - Hen-Hez (File-cabinet 3, Drawer 3, Folder 105)
    Henderson, Napoleon Jones; Henderson, William Penhollow; Henghes, Henny; Henneous, Mary H.; Henner, Jean-Jacques, 1829-1905; Henri, Robert, 1865-1929; Henrich, Albert; Henrique, Antonio; Henry, Joe; Henry, Michel, 1922-2002; Hentia, Sava, 1848-1904; Heppenstall, George R. M.; Hepworth, Barbara, 1903-1975; Herbin, Auguste, 1882-1960; Herbo, Fernand; Hering, Henry, 1814-1893; Herko, Berthold M.; Herman, Josef, 1911-2000; Hershman, Lynn, 1941-; Herter, Albert, 1871-1950; Herzog, Herman, 1831-1932; Herzog, Richard; Hesse, Eva, 1936-1970; Hetzel, Lila B.; Hewitt, Charles
  - Hf-Hiz (File-cabinet 3, Drawer 3, Folder 106)
    Higby, Wayne; Higgins, Eugene, 1874-1958; Hild, Robert; Hiler, Hilaire, 1898-1966; Hill, Clinton, 1922-2003; Hill, Derek, 1916-2000; Hill, John William, 1812-1879; Hindson, Bradley; Hinks, Christianne; Hinterreiter, Hans, 1902-1989; Hiroshige, Utagawa; Hirsch, Gilan; Hirsch, Joseph, 1910-1981; Hirsch, Stefan, 1899-1964; Hixson, Gary
  - Hj-Hok (File-cabinet 3, Drawer 3, Folder 107)
    Hnizdovsky, Jacques, 1915-1985; Hockney, David, 1937-; Hodgkin, Howard; Hodicke, KH; Hoffman, Richard P.; Hofman, Hans O., 1893-1973; Hokusai, Katsushika
  - Hol-Hoo (File-cabinet 3, Drawer 3, Folder 108)
    Holbrook, Hollis, 1909-1984; Holgate, Jeanne; Holland, Harry, 1911-1996; Hollander, Irwin; Hollar, Wenceslaus,1607-1677; Hollen-Bolmgren, Donna; Holley, Douglas; Hollon, Belle; Holt, Martha A.; Hölzel, Adolf, 1853-1934; Honegger, Gottfried, 1917-; Hood, Dorothy, 1918-2000; Hoog, Bernard de; Hook, Dorothy
  - Hop-Hul (File-cabinet 3, Drawer 3, Folder 109)
    Includes Edward Hopper exhibition catalog: "Edward Hopper: an exhibition of paintings, watercolors and etchings" 1937, Carnegie Institute.
    Hopkins, D. M. (David Moody), 1921-2001; Hopper, Edward, 1882-1967; Hoppner, John, 1758-1810; Hornby, Lester G. (Lester George), 1882-1956; Horton, William S., 1865-1936; Houlihan, Elena Hiatt; Howard, David; Howard, John G. (John George), 1803-1890; Howard, Wing; Howell, Karen; Hryshchenko, Oleksa, 1883-1977 (listed on materials as Gritchenko, Alexis); Hsien, Hung, 1933-; Hubert, Thomas P.; Huet, J.-B. (Jean-Baptiste), 1769-1823; Huezo, Roberto, 1947-; Hugnet, Georges, 1906-1974; Hulbeck, Charles Richard, 1892-1974; Huldah; Hull, Gregory; Hultberg, John, 1922-2005
  - Hum-Hz (File-cabinet 3, Drawer 3, Folder 110)
    Hum, Chi Ngih; Humblot, Robert, 1907-1962; Humes, Ralph Hamilton; Humphrey, Ralph, 1932-1990; Hunt, Richard, 1935-; Hunter, Clare Alice; Hunter, John, 1934-; Hunter, Ward; Huntington, Anna Hyatt, 1876-1973; Huntington, Jim; Hurd, Peter, 1904-1984; Hurtado, Angel, 1927-; Husain, Maqbool Fida
  - Ia-Iz (File-cabinet 3, Drawer 3, Folder 111)
    Includes reproductions and provenance information for two paintings by George Inness sold through the American Art Association, January 17, 1917, NY: "Sunset" and "Gathering Clouds."
    Ikeda, Masuo, 1934-1997; Ikegawa, Shiro, 1933-; Indiana, Robert, 1928-; Inness, George, 1825-1894; Inoue, Teruko, 1942-; Insley, Will, 1929-2011; Ipcar, Dahlov Zorach, 1917-; Ipoleto, Angelo; Ipoustéguy, Jean, 1920-2006; Ireland, Patrick, 1920-; Irish-Hosler, Doug; Irish-Hosler, Penny; Iselin, Lewis; Isenburger, Eric, 1902-1994; Iskovitz, Ben; Isola, Giancarlo, 1927-; Israëls, Jozef, 1824-1911; Ives, Norman, 1923-1978; Iwamiya, Takeji, 1920-; Izquierdo, Domingo, 1931-
  - Jaa-Jam (File-cabinet 3, Drawer 3, Folder 112)
    Jaar, Alfredo; Jackson, Charles M., 1929-; Jackson, Harry, 1924-2011; Jackson, Lee; Jacobson, Karl; Jácome Durango, Ramiro; Jacque, Charles Emile, 1813-1894; Jacquet, Alain, 1939-2008; Jaenisch, Hans, 1907-1989; Jagger, Gillian, 1930-; Jameson, Marcia; Jamison, Philip, 1925-
  - Jan-Johnson (File-cabinet 3, Drawer 3, Folder 113)
    Jaques, Francis Lee, 1887-1969; Gómez Jaramillo, Ignacio, 1910-1970; Jaramillo, Luciano, 1938-1984; Jarrell, Wadsworth, 1929-; Jarvis, John Wesley, 1780-1840; Jawlensky, Alexej von, 1864-1941; Jay, Paul; Jenkins, Jim; Jennerjahn, Warren Pete; Jennewein, Carl Paul, 1890-1978; Jenschel, Len; Jensen, Alfred, 1903-1981; Jessup, Fred; Jessup, Georgia; Jiminez, Luis; Jiménez, Manuel, 1935-; Johansen, Herman; John, Augustus, 1878-1961; Johnson, Buffie; Johnson, Cletus; Johnson, Eastman, 1824-1906; Johnson, Guy, 1927-; Johnson, Lester, 1919-2010; Johnson, Lynn; Johnson, Oliver, 1948-; Johnson, Philip, 1906-2005; Johnson, Ray; Johnson, William H., 1901-1970
  - Johnston-Jon (File-cabinet 3, Drawer 3, Folder 114)